{
  "swedish": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Jobba",
      "rightAnswer": "arbeta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "springa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Löpa",
      "rightAnswer": "springa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skutta",
      "rightAnswer": "hoppa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["springa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Anteckna",
      "rightAnswer": "skriva",
      "wrongAnswer": ["läsa", "måla", "rita"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Promenera",
      "rightAnswer": "gå",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Teckna",
      "rightAnswer": "rita",
      "wrongAnswer": ["måla", "klippa", "klistra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Färglägga",
      "rightAnswer": "måla",
      "wrongAnswer": ["rita", "klippa", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klippa",
      "rightAnswer": "skära",
      "wrongAnswer": ["klistra", "måla", "läsa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klistra",
      "rightAnswer": "limma",
      "wrongAnswer": ["klippa", "rita", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Konstruera",
      "rightAnswer": "bygga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["riva", "klippa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Simma",
      "rightAnswer": "bada",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "springa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Upptäcka",
      "rightAnswer": "hitta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Sova",
      "rightAnswer": "vila",
      "wrongAnswer": ["vakna", "springa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vakna",
      "rightAnswer": "stiga upp",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sova", "äta", "springa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Förtära",
      "rightAnswer": "äta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dricka", "sova", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klunka",
      "rightAnswer": "dricka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["äta", "sova", "hoppa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Snyfta",
      "rightAnswer": "gråta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Gunga",
      "rightAnswer": "svänga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["springa", "leka", "skutta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Kasta",
      "rightAnswer": "slänga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skriva", "måla", "simma"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Sjunga",
      "rightAnswer": "tralla",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dansa", "hoppa", "spela"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Boll",
      "rightAnswer": "kula",
      "wrongAnswer": ["docka", "bil", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Kofta",
      "rightAnswer": "tröja",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sko", "väska", "cykel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bil",
      "rightAnswer": "fordon",
      "wrongAnswer": ["boll", "docka", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Roman",
      "rightAnswer": "bok",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "boll", "docka"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skepp",
      "rightAnswer": "båt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "cykel", "väska"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bädd",
      "rightAnswer": "säng",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "bord", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Läroanstalt",
      "rightAnswer": "skola",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "parken", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Föda",
      "rightAnswer": "mat",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dryck", "penna", "boll"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Grönområde",
      "rightAnswer": "park",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Affär",
      "rightAnswer": "butik",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "parken"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Jycke",
      "rightAnswer": "hund",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vän",
      "rightAnswer": "kompis",
      "wrongAnswer": ["fiende", "hund", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Springare",
      "rightAnswer": "häst",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "hund", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Blomma",
      "rightAnswer": "växt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "penna", "cykel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Fjäderfä",
      "rightAnswer": "fågel",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "hund"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skär",
      "rightAnswer": "rosa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["blå", "gul", "grön"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vacker",
      "rightAnswer": "fin",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ful", "liten", "snabb"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Jättelik",
      "rightAnswer": "stor",
      "wrongAnswer": ["liten", "smal", "tunn"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Kvick",
      "rightAnswer": "snabb",
      "wrongAnswer": ["långsam", "tråkig", "seg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Saktfärdig",
      "rightAnswer": "långsam",
      "wrongAnswer": ["snabb", "arg", "alert"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Glad",
      "rightAnswer": "lycklig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ledsen", "arg", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Ledsen",
      "rightAnswer": "sorgsen",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Arg",
      "rightAnswer": "förbannad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Trött",
      "rightAnswer": "utmattad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["pigg", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Alert",
      "rightAnswer": "pigg",
      "wrongAnswer": ["trött", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Stark",
      "rightAnswer": "kraftig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["svag", "skör", "liten"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Svag",
      "rightAnswer": "skör",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stark", "kraftig", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Het",
      "rightAnswer": "varm",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kall", "glad", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bred",
      "rightAnswer": "vid",
      "wrongAnswer": ["smal", "tunn", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tunn",
      "rightAnswer": "smal",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bred", "rolig", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    }
  ]
}

